A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 2000-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series VII. Legislative Files, 2001-2005., Extent: 9.5 cu. ft. (Box 52-78)
  - Legislative Files, 2002.
    - Senate Bills: SB 647 - SB 649. (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Senate Bills: SB 650 - SB 691. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Joint Bills: HJ 62 - HJ 119. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Joint Bills: HJ 120 - HJ 250. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Joint Bills: SJ 39 - SJ 101. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Carry-over Bills. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Key Accomplishments--First 100 Days in Office. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Key Accomplishments--First 100 Days in Office. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - First 100 Days Report. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - First 100 Days Report. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - House Committee Information. (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Action Summaries and Bill Tracking Information (electronic). (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Parole Board Restructuring (SB 647). (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Parole Board Restructuring (SB 647). (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Parole Board Restructuring (SB 647). (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Prefiled Bills. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Racial Profiling Legislation (HB 1053). (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Racial Profiling Legislation (HB 1053). (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Racial Profiling Legislation (HB 1053). (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Racial Profiling Legislation (HB 1053). (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Racial Profiling Legislation (HB 1053). (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Racial Profiling Legislation (HB 1053). (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Reviews of Bills. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Senate Joint Resolutions for Follow-Up. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Files, 2003.
    - House Bills: HB 1379 - HB 1385. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 1392 - HB 1403. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 1412 - HB 1429. (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 1430 - HB 1435. (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 1436 - HB 1466. (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 1480 - HB 1501. (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 1502 - HB 1516. (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 1520 - HB 1524. (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 1527 - HB 1531. (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 1533 - HB 1555. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 1557 - HB 1565. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 1570 - HB 1574. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 1576 - HB 1607. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 1612 - HB 1641. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 1652 - HB 1670. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 1677 - HB 1683. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 1684 - HB 1702. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 1717 - HB 1744. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 1752 - HB 1783. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 1786 - HB 1811. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 1817 - HB 1842. (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 1845 - HB 1865. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 1878 - HB 1893. (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 1902 - HB 1905. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 1907 - HB 1912. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 1915 - HB 1922. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 1923. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 1924 - HB 1944. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 1952 - HB 1981. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 1985 - HB 1997. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 1999 - HB 2000. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 2001 - HB 2007. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 2008 - HB 2018. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 2019 - HB 2049. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 2061 - HB 2102. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 2108 - HB 2118. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 2121 - HB 2130. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 2155 - HB 2175. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 2179 - HB 2182. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 2190 - HB 2226. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 2229 - HB 2231. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 2232 - HB 2245. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 2246 - HB 2265. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 2273 - HB 2281. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 2282 - HB 2290. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 2293 - HB 2330. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 2336 - HB 2379. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 2384 - HB 2410. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 2411 - HB 2430. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 2431 - HB 2444. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 2445. (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 2446 - HB 2460. (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 2461 - HB 2510. (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 2511 - HB 2518. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 2529 - HB 2542. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 2546 - HB 2578. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 2585 - HB 2614. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 2615 - HB 2622. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 2624 - HB 2657. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 2660 - HB 2677. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 2680 - HB 2685. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 2686 - HB 2733. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 2734 - HB 2765. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 2766 - HB 2795. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 2798 - HB 2826. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bills: SB 694 - SB 705. (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Senate Bills: SB 707 - SB 712. (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Senate Bills: SB 716 - SB 739. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Senate Bills: SB 744 - SB 770. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Senate Bills: SB 771 - SB 798. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Senate Bills: SB 810 - SB 817. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Senate Bills: SB 819 - SB 843. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills: SB 846 - SB 865. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Senate Bills: SB 894 - SB 952. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills: SB 956. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bills: SB 964 - SB 972. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Senate Bills: SB 979. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Senate Bills: SB 984 - SB 996. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1001 - SB 1019. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1022 - SB 1060. (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1065 - SB 1077. (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1078 - SB 1119. (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1129 - SB 1136. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1138 - SB 1139. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1140 - SB 1143. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1144 - SB 1146. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1147 - SB 1151. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1153 - SB 1162. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1164 - SB 1190. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1199 - SB 1210. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1232 - SB 1234. (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1239. (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1240. (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1241 - SB 1251. (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1254 - SB 1269. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1296 - SB 1325. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1332. (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1336 - SB 1345. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Joint Bills: HJ 588. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Agency Bills and Accomplishments. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Bill Tracking Information. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Bill Tracking Information. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Proposals. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Proposals. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Proposals. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Notes and Correspondence Related to General Assembly. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Files, 2004.
    - House Bills: HB 1 - HB 41. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 43 - HB 71. (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 79 - HB 112. (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 118 - HB 130. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 143 - HB 167. (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 173 - HB 189. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 191 - HB 514. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 215 - HB 226. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 227 - HB 234. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 238 - HB 250. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 253 - HB 286. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 291 - HB 323. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 324 - HB 347. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 349 - HB 367. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 371 - HB 378. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 382 - HB 402. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 404 - HB 415. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 416 - HB 457. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 481 - HB 506. (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 507 - HB 530. (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 534 - HB 556. (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - House Bills: HB 564 - HB 570. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 571 - HB 578. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 589 - HB 595. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 598 - HB 631. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 638 - HB 645. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 646 - HB 654. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 655 - HB 663. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 664 - HB 671. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 674 - HB 652. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 724 - HB 755. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 756 - HB 765. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 768 - HB 779. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 783 - HB 790. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 792 - HB 810. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 815 - HB 863. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 865 - HB 872. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 873 - HB 916. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 927 - HB 946. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 948 - HB 962. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 982 - HB 1012. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 1025 - HB 1042. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 1053 - HB 1054. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 1055 - HB 1057. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 1058 - HB 1059. (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 1060 - HB 1074. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 1080 - HB 1096. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 1105 - HB 1125. (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 1126 - HB 1140. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 1142 - HB 1147. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 1148 - HB 1193. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 1195 - HB 1205. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 1209 - HB 1232. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 1233 - HB 1234. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 1237 - HB 1249. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 1250 - HB 1299. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 1302 - HB 1308. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 1309 - HB 1316. (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 1317 - HB 1344. (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 1355 - HB 1392. (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 1394 - HB 1425. (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 1430. (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 1443 - HB 1481. (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 1482 - HB 1489. (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Senate Bills: SB 6 - SB 40. (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Senate Bills: SB 43 - SB 72. (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Senate Bills: SB 75 - SB 90. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Senate Bills: SB 92 - SB 99. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Senate Bills: SB 100 - SB 136. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Senate Bills: SB 141 - SB 202. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Senate Bills: SB 214 - SB 234. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills: SB 235 - SB 237. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Senate Bills: SB 238 - SB 287. (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills: SB 293 - SB 317. (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bills: SB 318 - SB 321. (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Senate Bills: SB 325 - SB 329. (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Senate Bills: SB 331 - SB 339. (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bills: SB 341 - SB 376. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bills: SB 384 - SB 410. (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Senate Bills: SB 421 - SB 448. (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Senate Bills: SB 469 - SB 485. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Senate Bills: SB 487 - SB 492. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Senate Bills: SB 493 - SB 551. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Senate Bills: SB 552 - SB 577. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Senate Bills: SB 579 - SB 592. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills: SB 593 - SB 617. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Senate Bills: SB 622 - SB 648. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills: SB 657 - SB 677. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bills: SB 685 - SB 693. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Joint Bills: HJ 79 - HJ 291. (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Joint Bills: SJ 81 - SJ 106. (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Agency Legislation and Talking Points. (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Agency Legislation and Talking Points. (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Bill Tracking Information. (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Bill Tracking Information. (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Bill Tracking Information. (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Bill Tracking Information. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Carry Over Legislation: HB 134 - HB 157. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Carry Over Legislation: HB 170 - HB 435. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Carry Over Legislation: HB 452 - HB 614. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Carry Over Legislation: HB 616 - HB 636. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Department of Emergency Management Legislative Liasons. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - General Assembly Information. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Package. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Legislative Package. (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Proposed Legislation: Alcoholic Beverage Control. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Legislation: Correctional Education. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Proposed Legislation: Corrections. (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Proposed Legislation: Criminal Justice Services. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Proposed Legislation: Emergency Management. (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Proposed Legislation: Fire Programs. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Proposed Legislation: Juvenile Justice. (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Proposed Legislation: Miliary Affairs. (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Proposed Legislation: State Police. (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Files, 2005.
    - House Bills: HB 1156 - HB 1502. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 1511 - HB 1542. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 1547 - HB 1576. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 1587 - HB 1616. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 1618 - HB 1673. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 1674 - HB 1688. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 1690 - HB 1720. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 1721 - HB 1737. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 1739 - HB 1756. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 1761 - HB 1796. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 1799 - HB 1828. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 1830 - HB 1861. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 1867 - HB 1879. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 1883 - HB 1915. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 1917 - HB 1948. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 1950 - HB 1974. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 1976 - HB 1995. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 1997 - HB 2009. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 2015 - HB 2028. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 2032 - HB 2059. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 2060 - HB 2095. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 2103 - HB 2130. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 2139 - HB 2173. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 2175 - HB 2195. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 2199 - HB 2213. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 2214 - HB 2216. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 2217 - HB 2247. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 2248 - HB 2256. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 2258 - HB 2291. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 2301 - HB 2315. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 2318 - HB 2327. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 2329 - HB 2369. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 2379 - HB 2409. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 2417 - HB 2437. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 2438 - HB 2467. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 2471 - HB 2504. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 2508 - HB 2535. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 2542 - HB 2565. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 2569 - HB 2613. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 2623 - HB 2634. (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 2638 - HB 2652. (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 2653 - HB 2665. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 2667 - HB 2674. (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 2678 - HB 2704. (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 2707 - HB 2712. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 2722 - HB 2740. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 2741 - HB 2791. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 2802 - HB 2823. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 2830 - HB 2854. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 2869 - HB 2890. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 2891 - HB 2906. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 2915 - HB 2928. (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 2931 - HB 2935. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bills: SB 710 - SB 726. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Senate Bills: SB 732 - SB 784. (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Senate Bills: SB 800 - SB 814. (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bills: SB 818 - SB 833. (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bills: SB 840 - SB 863. (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Senate Bills: SB 865 - SB 895. (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Senate Bills: SB 901 - SB 943. (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Senate Bills: SB 954 - SB 988. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Senate Bills: SB 997 - SB 1015. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1020 - SB 1067. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1070 - SB 1095. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1101 - SB 1131. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1133 - SB 1151. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1153. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1155 - SB 1164. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1168 - SB 1207. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1209 - SB 1280. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1302 - SB 1333. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bills: SB 1339 - SB 1346. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Joint Bills: HJ 573 - HJ 703. (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Joint Bills: SJ 273 - SJ 387. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - C.U.R.E. Bills: HB 1713 - HB 2108. (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - C.U.R.E. Bills: HB 2369 - HJ 749. (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - C.U.R.E. Bills: SB 805 - SJ 287. (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Legislative Package. (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Package. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Proposals (submissions to Secretary). (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Proposals (submissions to Secretary). (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Proposals (full Public Safety submission package). (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Proposals (full Public Safety submission package). (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Proposals (full Public Safety submission package). (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Proposals (full Public Safety submission package). (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Legislative Proposals (full Public Safety submission package). (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Proposals (full Public Safety submission package). (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Proposals (full Public Safety submission package). (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Proposals (misc.). (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Proposals (misc.). (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Woodrum Amendment (HB 2291). (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Series VIII. Public Relations Files, 2001-2005., Extent: .53 cu. ft. (Box 79-80)
  Contains correspondence and scheduling material related to events and speaking engagements attended by Secretary of Public Safety, John Marshall. Most of this series is comprised of event correspondence, both internal and external, regarding Secretary Marshall's public appearances.
  The public relations files are arranged alphabetically by folder title, and chronologically within.
  - Event Correspondence, 2002 January-April. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Event Correspondence, 2002 April. (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Event Correspondence, 2002 May. (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Event Correspondence, 2002 June-August. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Event Correspondence, 2002 September-December. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Event Correspondence, 2003 January-May. (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Event Correspondence, 2003 June-August. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Event Correspondence, 2003 September-December. (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Event Correspondence, 2004 January-July. (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Event Correspondence, 2004 August-September. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Event Correspondence, 2004 October-December. (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Event Correspondence, 2005 January-March. (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Event Correspondence, 2005 April-August. (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Event Correspondence, 2005 September-December. (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Governor's Event Schedule Requests, 2002. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Letters of Congratulation, 2001-2002. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Scheduled Events, 2002. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Scheduled Events, 2002-2003. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Scheduled Events--Correctional Officer's Week, 2003. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Speaking Engagements, 2002-2005. (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Series IX. Secretary's Correspondence, 2002-2006., Extent: 1.9 cu. ft. (Box 81-86)
  Contains correspondence files kept by the Secretary of Public Safety during the administration of Governor Mark R. Warner. These files are different than the constituent correspondence, though they do contain some correspondence between the Secretary and various constituents. Most of the constituent letters are in regard to Department of Corrections inmates and the activities of the Parole Board. This series also contains internal correspondence and memos between the Secretary and other state agencies, as well as agencies within the Public Safety secretariat, and members of the Public Safety office itself. This series contains restricted information that has either been redacted or sealed. The material may include, but is not limited to, medical records, social security numbers, Department of Corrections inmate classification material, and Parole Board review documents.
  The Secretary's correspondence is arranged alphabetically, and is chronologically reversed within each folder. If there are multiple folders for one letter, each folder is individually numbered (e.g., 1 of 3, 2 of 3, 3 of 3). The first folder for any letter will contain the latest correspondence and the last folder will contain the earliest.
  - A, 2002-2005 (1 of 2). (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - A, 2002-2005 (2 of 2). (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - B, 2002-2005 (1 of 6). (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - B, 2002-2005 (2 of 6). (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - B, 2002-2005 (3 of 6). (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - B, 2002-2005 (4 of 6). (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - B, 2002-2005 (5 of 6). (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - B, 2002-2005 (6 of 6). (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - C, 2002-2005 (1 of 4). (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - C, 2002-2005 (2 of 4). (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - C, 2002-2005 (3 of 4). (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - C, 2002-2005 (4 of 4). (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - D, 2002-2006 (1 of 2). (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - D, 2002-2006 (2 of 2). (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - E, 2002-2005. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - F, 2002-2005 (1 of 3). (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - F, 2002-2005 (2 of 3). (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - F, 2002-2005 (3 of 3). (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - G, 2002-2005 (1 of 2). (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - G, 2002-2005 (2 of 2). (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - H, 2002-2006 (1 of 6). (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - H, 2002-2006 (2 of 6). (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - H, 2002-2006 (3 of 6). (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - H, 2002-2006 (4 of 6). (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - H, 2002-2006 (5 of 6). (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - H, 2002-2006 (6 of 6). (Box 82, Folder 14)